so let's discuss the answer for our
manufacturing cost quiz we had a watch
processor that was one millimeter square
in size and a laptop processor that is a
hundred millimeter squares in size the
question was which of the following is
true is the cost of the laptop processor
about 100 times the cost of a watch
processor is it more than that or less
than that we have seen already that if
we disregard the yield the cost of a
laptop processor would be about 100
times the cost of a watch processor just
because the same cost wafer gets divided
into a hundred more of these than of
these however larger processors also
result in lower yield so this is why the
cost of a laptop processor will be more
than proportionately at the cost of the
watch processor and this is the correct
answer